Nhan Thien

Data Analyst | Male | Single | 19 December 1988

Experience 3 years

Latest company Yomedia as Data Analyst

Highest education Bachelors

Languages English - Intermediate

Email hothiennhanit@gmail.com

Phone 0966012989

Address 97/2 Ung Văn Khiêm, Binh Thanh, Ho

Chi Minh City

Preferred working Ho Chi Minh

location

Job IT - Software | IT - Software

industries/functions

Expected job level Experienced (non-manager)

Expected salary 100

(USD)

Preferred benefit

SUMMARY

I want to get challenges, a new technology. Such as: Natural Languague Processing, Recommendation Systems, AI, Deeplearing



for NLP (LSTM). Data minning, Data analyst, Data sciencetist. Striving to become the product manager. Learn more things when working in companies to accumulate much experience for future promotion. Mobility Developer (iOS-Android) Business Analysis Recommendation System Big Data - Socail Network Analyst

Python - Flask

Have some sample project on Github : https://github.com/NhanThien/VRA

RestAPI using DeepLearing (CNN) to classification image (nude & not_nude): https://github.com/NhanThien/RestAPIKeras

SKILL

- Developer
- Java
- Business Analyst
- PHP
- iOS
- English Proficiency
- Business Development
- Mobile
- Android
- Python
- Insurance
- Pl/sql
- iOS Developer
- Mobile Development
- Jira
- Zend



- Business Analysis
- Data Science
- English & Japanese
- IT Phần Mềm
- Xcode
- Android, iOS
- Phân Tích
- Javascript Jquery
- English: Listening, Speaking, Reading, Writing
- Data Analysis & Statistic Software
- Mind Map
- GUI Design / Software Design
- English Verbal and Written
- Credit Lending, Risk Management
- Knowledge Of IT
- Software Development
- .NET C#
- Developer, Business Analyst, Project Manager
- Software Engineer, QA Engineer
- Data Scientist
- ERP, Sms, SCM
- MS Dynamic, Navision, AX Or SAP
- Product Evaluation and Development
- Product Marketing & Opcos Marketing
- Dbms
- Beacon
- Computer Science Information Technology
- Lập Trình iOS Sdk
- Lập Trình Giao Diện Trên iPhone
- IT Sofware
- Process and Policy



WORK EXPERIENCE

May 2018 - Now

Data Analyst

Yomedia

I apply Machine Learning for resolve problem business, such as : text classification, topic modeling and demographic user.

Dec 2016 - May 2018

Software Engineer

MediaStep Software

Nov 2015 - Dec 2016

Senior iOS Mobile Developer

Keaz Pty Ltd

Phát triển ứng dụng KeazAccess (iOS) Phát triển ứng dụng EDNAVALET (iOS): http://www.ednavalet.com/ (release on AppStore) Phát triển ứng dụng Taxi like Uber - Grab

EDUCATION

Jul 2018 - Jul 2018

Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning

Others - Đại học Tân Tạo

Khoá học hè về Trí tuệ nhân tạo và học máy (Summer school on



Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning)

Thời gian: 9 – 13 tháng 7 năm 2018.

Địa điểm: Đại học Tân Tạo – Đức Hoà, Long An Đơn vị tổ chức: Khoa Kỹ Thuật – ĐH Tân Tạo http://soe.ttu.edu.vn/summer_school/1758/

Sep 2017 - Nov 2017

VRA - Nhận Dạng Thị Giác Và Ứng Dụng

Others - University of Information Technology - UIT

Development Image Classification

https://github.com/NhanThien/VRA/tree/master/Report_Final

Result: 9.3/10

Feb 2016 - Mar 2016

Hoàn thành mọi việc với Kanban

Others - Hoc viện Agile

Hoc online Udemy.

Dec 2014 - Jan 2015

Business Analysis

Others - BAC Center - CÔNG TY TNHH ĐÀO TẠO VÀ TƯ VẤN BAC

Business Analysis

Sep 2007 - Nov 2012

Công nghệ thông tin

Bachelors - Đại Học Tôn Đức Thắng



REFERENCE

Nguyễn Hải Trung

IT Coordinator at **AFE Solutions**haitrung3005@gmail.com | 0976614876

